<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>INDRO SPINELLI</title>
    <link>https://spindro.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on INDRO SPINELLI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 by Indro Spinelli. &lt;a href=&#39;https://spindro.github.io/privacy&#39;&gt;Privacy policy&lt;/a&gt;.</copyright><atom:link href="https://spindro.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://spindro.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spindro.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Experience 2023-**** Assistant Professor Department of Computer Science, Sapienza University of Rome 2022-2023 Research Fellow INFN, Istituto Nazionale di Fisica Nucleare CINI, Consorzio Interuniversitario Nazionale per l&amp;rsquo;Informatica 2022-2023 Teaching Assistant LUISS, Department of Business and Management 2017-2018 Research Intern Alcor lab, Sapienza University of Rome Education 2019-2022 PhD Information and Communication Technologies Sapienza University of Rome / UiT The Arctic University of Norway 2017-2019 MSc Artificial Intelligence and Robotics Sapienza University of Rome 2014-2017 BSc Computer and System Engineering Sapienza University of Rome CV Here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTIVITIES</title>
      <link>https://spindro.github.io/activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spindro.github.io/activities/</guid>
      <description>Talks LoG MeetUp Trento Explainable Graph Neural Networks Università della Svizzera Italiana Fair Graph Representation Learning Roma Tre University Graph Machine Learning Reviewing I am serving as Associate Editor for The Visual Computer.
I have been involved as reviewer for the following AI conferences and journals:
Conferences International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) IEEE World Congress on Computational Intelligence (WCCI) Association for the Advancement of Artificial Intelligence (AAAI) International Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Statistics (AISTATS) IEEE / CVF Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition Conference (CVPR) European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV) Journals IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems IEEE Transactions on Artificial Intelligence Neural Networks, Elsevier Neurocomputing, Elsevier Cognitive Computation, Springer Neural Processing Letters, Springer </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://spindro.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spindro.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Links to other websites Other websites referenced here may collect information about you, use cookies, embed additional tracking services from third parties, and record your interaction with that embedded content, including your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are signed in to that website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PUBLICATIONS</title>
      <link>https://spindro.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spindro.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Journals Machine Un-learning: An Overview of Techniques, Applications, and Future Directions
S Sai, U Mittal, V Chamola, K Huang, I Spinelli, S Scardapane, Z Tan, A Hussain Cognitive Computation	2024 Machine Un-learning: An Overview of Techniques, Applications, and Future Directions
Interpreting black-box models: a review on explainable artificial intelligence
V Hassija, V Chamola, A Mahapatra, A Singal, D Goel, K Huang, S Scardapane, I Spinelli, M Mahmud, A Hussain Cognitive Computation	2023 Drop Edges and Adapt: a Fairness Enforcing Fine-tuning for Graph Neural Networks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEACHING</title>
      <link>https://spindro.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spindro.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>AA. 2023/2024 Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence Unit 1 Applied Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence, Sapienza University of Rome. Course Material
Thesis We pursuing several projects in the following research areas: Embodied AI, Human Motion Generation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
